

CONTACT INFO

E-mail: jakedaigle3.14@gmail.com WhatsApp: +33 6 66 36 11 93 Address: Lund 224 68

ABOUT ME

I am a 21 year old Canadian living in Sweden. I came here to learn about a new culture, embrace the diverse opportunities abound, and hopefully kickstart my career.

Fueled by my passions for interdisciplinary research, sustainability, optimization, efficiency, and innovation, I hope to one day be working at the forefront of new technologies.

LANGUAGES

- English Native
- French Intermediate
- LaTeX (2 years)
- Python (1 year)
- C (1 year)
- Mathematica (1 year)

REFERENCES

Available upon request.

WORK EXPERIENCE

MATH/PHYSICS RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Lakehead University - CANADA | May 2022 -Oct 2023

- Documenting ideas, proofs, and findings in LaTeX
- Research in dimension groups
- Research in immanants of matrices and various relevant statistical features in relation to the boson sampling problem
- Worked in groups with coworkers and field experts, as well as independently

MATH TUTOR/MARKER

Lakehead University / Freelance - CANADA | Oct 22 - Jun 2023

- Grading and feedback for large classes
- 1-on-1 personalized lessons for struggling students

STARTUP V.P. OF I.T.

FrosTek of J.A. Canada - CANADA | Oct 2016 - Jun 2017

- · Social media creation and maintenance
- Statistical analysis and presentation of company data
- Assisting in creating and distributing advertisements
- General technology management and maintenance

EDUCATION

HONOURS BSC MATHEMATICS, MINOR PHYSICS

Lakehead University - CANADA | Sept 2019-April 2023

SKILLS

- Math
 - Statistical analysis
 - Data analysis
 - Formulaic modelling and problem solving
 - Optimization
 - Fractal geometry
- Physics
 - Quantum mechanics
- Writing technical reports
 - LaTeX, Overleaf, Beamer, Mathematica
- Programming (languages on left)
 - Creative code refactoring to enhance efficiency and optimize resource allocation and computation time
- Presentation of research
- Gardening, woodworking, machine operation, general labour